Soubhagya Kumar Barik (1) Featured



Application Developer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Application Maintenance, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution

Architecture, PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, CakePHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, iQuery, Ajax.



Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 6 Month(s) Current Designation: Application Developer -PHP

Current Company: Reliance jio Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bhubaneshwar, Bengaluru / Bangalore Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Application Developer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Application

Support, Project Management, Requirement Analysis, Solution

Architecture, PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, CakePHP, WordPress, MySQL, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

4.6 years of experience in web technologies like PHP, Cakephp ,Laravel,Lumen MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax ,Redis, REST API, SOAP API, AWS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap etc.

Able to focus on specific tasks, keeping overall project goals in mind.

Can be counted on to complete assignments without supervision.

Ability and willingness to learn new things fast.

Willingness to lead projects and see them through to completion.

Willingness to work on new technologies.

Ability to finish work modules within tight deadlines.

Work Experience

Reliance jio as Application Developer -PHP Jul 2020 to Till Date

Complete ownership of microservices which is the backbone of the JIO tv application.

Dailyhunt as Software Developer

Mar 2019 to Jul 2020

Engaged in Dailyhunt Ad Service platform for feature upgrade & performance fixes.

Carmatec IT Solutions as Software Engineer

May 2018 to Mar 2019

Requirement gathering phase to delivery of the product.

MagniGeeks Technologies as Web Developer

Feb 2017 to Mar 2018

Involved in multiple in-house product development.

Raddyx Technologies as Software Developer Jan 2016 to Feb 2017

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Utkal University in 2013

PG: MCA (Computers) from Biju Patnaik University of Technology (BPUT) in 2016

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PHP			
Laravel 8.x,Lumen 8.x,CakePHP			
CODEIGNITER			
MySQL, MS Access			
REST API, AWS			
XAMPP, LAMP			
Bootstrap, Materialize CSS			
Github, Bitbucket			
Gitlab, Filezilla, Sourcetree			
Trello, Asana, Azure			
Windows 7/8.1/10, Linux			
PHPStorm, VS Code, Netbeans IDE			
Sublime text			
MS Word, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Odia				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time